https://www.firstpeoples.com/privacy-policy

First Peoples Community FCU Privacy Policy
FACTS
WHAT DOES FIRST PEOPLES COMMUNITY FEDERAL CREDIT UNION DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand.
What?
The type of personal information we collect and share depends on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security number
Account balances and payment history
Credit history and credit score
How?
All financial companies need to share members' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members' personal information; the reasons First Peoples Community Federal Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information.
Does First Peoples share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes –
such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or to report to credit bureaus.
Yes
No
For our marketing purposes –
To offer our products and services to you.
Yes
No
For joint marketing with other financial companies
Yes
Yes
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes –
Information about your transactions and experiences.
Yes
No
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes –
Information about your creditworthiness.
No
Yes
For our affiliates to market you
Yes
Yes
For nonaffiliates to market you
Yes
Yes
To limit our sharing: Call 301-784-3000 or toll-free 1-800-655-8335
Please note: If you are a new member, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we send this notice. When you are no longer our member, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
Questions?
Call 301-784-3000 or
toll-free 1-800-655-8335
What We Do
How does First Peoples Community Federal Credit Union protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
We also maintain other physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect this information and we limit access to information to those employees for whom access is appropriate.
How does First Peoples Community Federal Credit Union collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
Open an account
Apply for a loan
Use your credit or debit card
We collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus.
Why can't I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
Sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your creditworthiness
Affiliates from using your information to market you
Sharing for non affiliates to market you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing (we do not share information about California residents).
What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?
Your choices will apply to everyone on your account - unless you tell us otherwise.
Definitions
Affiliates: Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies. Our affiliate offers:
Title insurance
Settlement services
Nonaffiliates: Companies not related by common bond ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies, such as:
Insurance agents
Life insurers
Property and casualty insurers
Investment brokers
Joint Marketing: A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products and services to you, such as:
Insurance agents
Life insurers
Property and casualty insurers
Investment brokers
